No living creature was
harmed during the filming.
Episode 78
You have done many treacheries.
You made my people, my brother...
and even the sultan turn back on me.
You are biting more than you can chew.
You will pay for your insolence with
your people and tribe.
But, your alps first.
What are you saying.
Setting a trap for the Seljuk vizier...
and drawing your weapons, huh?
You are walking up to your death, Osman.
Stop there, Konur!
Stay there!
We have your alps.
Don't make a mistake, Osman.
Or they'll be killed.
My alps!
Ya Allah!
Are my alps alive?
It depends on you, Osman Bey.
Speak.
Let Vizier Alemşah go.
If...
If you touch them...
I'll kill the vizier first, and
you last.
Enough, Osman. Lower your weapon.
Lower, so that I can behead
you only.
Let me go!
Let us go!
My bey!
My bey! We are here!
-Alps!
-We are here, my bey.
Step back.
Step back!
Now, move!
Soldiers!
My bey! My bey!
Brothers! Are you well?
We are, my bey.
Your alps are alive.
Let Vizier Alemşah go.
Or we'll kill them all.
My bey, kill him!
Don't think about us, my bey.
Kill the traitor!
Osman!
Brother, what are you doing?
I'm holding the head of your partner,
Gündüz Bey.
Don't, Osman.
If you kill the vizier, there is no
turning back, Osman.
Think for your alps.
Think for your tribe,
your tribe!
For my tribe, for my people...
should I be with a traitor like you?
You are disobeying the sultan's
orders!
Don't.
Look, Osman.
Surrender.
The sultan likes you.
Go to his presence and explain
yourself.
My cause is the cause of
the Turks.
This is such a sacred cause that...
there is no need to explain
it to anyone.
But...
even you failed to understand it.
Brother.
Don't, take another step.
I never miss an opportunity...
to kill you, Gündüz Bey.
Or, just go...
go...
Brother...
Osman.
You will pay for what you've done.
But you will never take my life.
Because you are merciful, Osman.
You can't sacrifice your brother
or your alps.
My bey, kill him.
Don't let him speak, my bey!
Your alps don't care about
their lives.
Gündüz Bey is brave.
What about your tribe?
If he kills me...
Konur, Ferman!
Turn Kayı Tribe into hell!
Don't leave a single tent unburnt...
and a single head not beheaded!
Orhan...
I will--
Of course, if Osman bey doesn't
do the mistake...
Not for what you've done...
even for just saying these things,
I'll rip you apart.
But...
but...
Not now.
Wait.
Wait, Vizier Alemşah.
Don't do it, my bey!
Not now, not then, Osman.
This is the end for you.
Let me think about tomorrow.
Finally.
Finally, the wolf is in the cage!
And the treacherous lion is
at the edge of my sword.
I'll take Nikola for what he did
to Mari.
Osman wants me to take him in when
he comes to Bilecik.
If we don't act with Osman, they'll
unite to destroy us.
Let's hope that.
Traitors!
Look at these lords!
Working together with Osman
to destroy me!
No one will move until Osman thinks that
he has won.
Let him think that he is
victorious.
I'll show him that I'm the greatest
of the helpless.
Now is the time to complete
the missing piece.
Julia, bring Rogatus.
Lord Rogatus, run!
We've been betrayed!
Damn it! Nikola!
I'll kill you with my hands.
Kosses, did you like my prisoner?
You never knew which side
to pick.
My side matters not, Nikola.
I will be the one to take your life.
Ours will be put to the dungeon.
Kosses, your verdict for the treason...
will be given by the emperor
in Constantinople.
You--
The lords are at the emperor's mercy.
Osman.
But you will be executed...
in this castle.
What are you saying, vizier Alemşah?
What execution?
Don't do this!
You can't do that!
My bey! My bey!
My bey!
Brother.
My old friend, let's go.
Take him.
Come, Gündüz Bey.
Come.
We'll talk.
What are you waiting for?
Find him!
Dishonorable!
We'll ask for this.
What are you doing?
There is nothing we can learn from them.
There is no need.
If you had smashed them enough
earlier, it wouldn't happen now.
Do your job well, Konur.
Dishonorable.
Bring him.
-Hang on, brother!
-Stop! Stop!
Let him go!
Weasels!
Let me go!
You vile dog!
Hang on, brother!
I will kill you!
You stand up against the vizier, huh?
That's enough for now.
I'll come back.
I save you for the last, Osman.
Don't hold back.
Julia.
What do you mean you couldn't
find him?
We couldn't.
We searched everywhere.
But that treacherous Rogatus ran away.
He can't go anywhere, Julia.
I don't like excuses.
You'll find him.
Don't...
bring me any more bad news.
Sir, as you ordered, Kosses is ready
to go to Constantinople.
I don't want any mistake.
I tasked our best soldiers, sir.
We'll take him there without
a problem.
Good.
Vizier Alemşah.
Osman wasn't right.
But execution?
You know it well, it is written in
Sultan's verdict that...
Osman will be trialed in Konya.
Now.
Even without a trial...
what is a execution?
You witnessed
what happened.
Osman put his sword at the neck
of the Seljuk vizier.
If I wasn't lucky, he would
kill me there.
Of course, it will be punished
with execution.
You are right.
Osman made a great mistake.
But everything should be in order.
What I ask from you is to let
Osman be trialed in Konya.
Is it so important for you
to keep Osman Alive?
Vizier Alemşah.
Osman is my brother.
My father Ertuğrul Ghazi left
him to me.
Whatever he does...
if you hurt him...
you'll face me...
and the whole of the Kayı Tribe.
You say so?
There is only one way to save Osman.
But you'll have a great
responsibility.
If you want Osman to live...
you'll become the bey
of the Kayı Tribe.
Not as a regent.
You'll be a real bey.
You'll gather the council and
sit on the throne.
And you'll be my right hand
on these lands.
Can you do this, Gündüz Bey?
I will.
If...
it'll save my brother's life...
I'll do anything.
Vizier Alemşah!
It's the promise of Ertuğrul Ghazi's
son, Gündüz Bey.
I'll do as you want.
Good, then.
Osman will be taken to Konya
to be trialed.
Alright.
If you allow me.
When Osman is this close to death...
we can't let him survive!
Vizier Alemşah, if you won't
be able to do this, I will!
If Osman is taken to Konya...
Calm down, Nikola.
We can't take this risk.
Osman will never be on the road.
He will die here.
Degenerate!
Do you think I won't avenge Gonca?
Do you think?
Osman!
Rogatus ran away.
But you and your soldiers...
will be in pain.
Take him out.
Don't touch him!
Take me and leave my bey!
Don't touch my bey!
Come at me!
Come at me, degenerates!
If we get freed...
you'll prefer hell...
to what we'll do to you.
Whip him good.
Until he can't dream of things
he can't do.
Let my bey go!
Hit!
Hang on, my bey!
Degenerates!
Hit!
Osman.
Osman. Osman.
Osman!
Osman! Osman!
Bala, my girl?
-Bala!
-Osman!
Bala, wake up!
Bala, wake up, my girl!
Mother! Mother!
Osman!
Calm down, my girl.
Bala Hatun. My lady, are you alright?
It was a dream, mother.
Bring water, Zehra.
It was a dream.
Osman was in darkness.
I don't feel good.
What if they hurt Osman?
Drink this.
Drink it.
It was a nightmare. You can't find
meanings in a nightmare.
Be at ease.
Thank you, Zehra.
Osman is alright.
Be at ease.
Vizier Alemşah wants Osman at
his presence.
Tie him up!
We don't know what he'll do.
Bilecik Castle.
I'll make you pay...
for what you did to Mari.
Nikola.
So, the reason for this betreyal
is your stupid sister, huh?
You convinced Rogatus too!
This insolence must be because
of your helplessness.
After all, if I was on my way to
the emperor to be trialed...
I would be mad like you.
But don't worry. You won't
be alone. After I get Rogatus...
I'll send him to you.
For my burnt market...
I have Harmankaya...
for myself!
Mine!
I, Aya Nikola...
the lord of İnegöl and Harmankaya!
You will beg me to kill you.
Did you hear me?
I will kill you.
A nothing!
What can he do to me?
Welcome, Osman Bey.
Come closer.
You became these lands that your
father Ertuğrul Ghazi left.
He had older brothers,
an uncle...
if they chose him as the leader...
he must be a great man, I would say.
But you turned out to be
quite a fool, Osman.
What righteous move,
or virtue...
do you find to be foolish?
Tell me.
You don't see the power balances.
Who am I?
The shadow of the Seljuks!
You are right.
Sultan Mesud is the sun.
You are his shadow.
You exist when he does,
and not when he doesn't.
Our existence doesn't depend on anyone
but Allah!
We aren't the shadow of
anyone.
You disobeyed the state's orders.
You drew your weapon against
your vizier.
You will pay for it all.
After I talk to Sultan Mesud...
he'll see the truth.
He'll be sorry that he gave someone
like you such a position.
Osman.
Who told you that you will
go to Konya?
Here. Here.
In Bilecik.
You will be...
hung!
And not only you.
All your alps.
I'll never kneel!
No one can make me kneel!
No one!
Setting an ambush to the
state's vizier, huh?
Drawing a weapon against
the vizier, huh?
Take him away!
You!
You are neither the state nor the
vizier of the state!
You baseborn!
There is treachery in your blood.
But sooner or later,
the truth will be revealed!
Either with us or without us!
Your end will come!
Osman is in my way, Konur.
We'll hang him tomorrow. His death
will be good for Gündüz and the Kayı.
Gündüz Bey won't allow this.
Do I need a permission?
What we say happens.
We'll tell Gündüz Bey that
we caught him running away.
And we hung him to not
provoke the lords.
My vizier, the sultan's verdict.
He makes sure that he wants him in Konya.
Let the sultan send orders from
his throne.
The sword was at my neck, Konur!
My decision is final.
Everything has a price.
This is the price of
revolting against...
Alemşah!
As you see fit, my vizier.
Who are you?
What do you want?
Some seek it, some just find it, Rogatus.
We were waiting for Osman Bey.
He would come from here
if anything went wrong.
You...
you are Father Philip.
My name isn't Philip.
We are on the righteous path!
We put our efforts for that only!
I'm Kumral Abdal.
I'm Osman Bey's comrade.
I heard that you are a friend.
Tell me, Rogatus. Why are you running
away from the castle.
Where is Osman Bey?
We were betrayed.
Osman Bey and Kosses are taken
captives.
I ran away.
What? What?
No!
Allah!
My bey!
The alps!
Alemşah! Ah!
What tricks have you
pulled again?
What tricks have you pulled
again?
He worked together with Nikola and
bought my soldiers.
My soldiers!
The one who took Prophet Joseph
out of that dungeon...
will surely take Osman Bey too!
We shouldn't stand here.
We are in the open now.
We need to hide.
Come on.
A wolf can't be a captive.
While we were trying to save
our brother...
he throws himself
to a well!
Speak it out!
Complete your sentence!
Mother!
Osman tried to kill the vizier!
An execution verdict is given!
Do you hear what you say, Gündüz Bey?
-What execution?
-Execution! Execution!
But hold on!
We'll see what other troubles Osman
will bring upon him.
While we were trying to
protect our brother...
and expect him to control
himself...
Would he? No! He runs to
even greater troubles!
What are you doing when your
brother is fighting the world, Gündüz?
Are you getting mad at your
brother there?
Mother!
For my brother's life...
I put myself there!
I saved him from the rope!
Bilecik Castle.
Jesus Christ heard our prayers!
Osman who killed our soldiers
will be hung at Bilecik today!
People!
The greatest heathen...
the greatest evil...
Osman and his alps will
be hung today!
Sacred children of Jesus Christ!
We'll take our revenge!
Ferman.
Nothing will go wrong.
Osman will die here today and here.
He will, my vizier.
Everything is prepared as you want.
Sacred children of Jesus Christ!
Our revenge will be taken.
Osman who killed our soldiers...
Still no trace of Rogatus?
We still haven't found him.
Find Rogatus, Julia.
Do everything for that.
Vizier listened to us...
and took the rope away from
Osman's neck.
Look at this.
That devil wouldn't work without
a return.
Did he take it off with
a single word of yours?
Speak! What did he want from
you in return, Gündüz?
What did you give the vizier that
he left Osman?
As the vizier says...
from now, I'll be the right hand
of Alemşah in these lands.
With his order...
the council will be gathered.
The tribe has a bey, Gündüz Bey.
What are you talking about?
I will never allow this!
Because you sat on the throne
for a few days...
you forgot the owner of the throne!
But we'll remind you! The throne you
sit on belongs to Osman Bey!
This tribe can't survive any other
fight for the throne.
Don't do this to your brother,
Gündüz Bey.
And what do you want?
Our tribe will be burnt down...
and people will be killed, is that it?
There were no other choice.
And not only me.
Get mad at Osman too.
If he didn't ran away...
if he went to the Sultan...
none of this would
ever happen!
Don't I know you a bit?
The Gündüz I know wouldn't do this.
He would stand behind
his brother.
Tell me.
Who is this?
That can't stand behind his brother.
Mother, don't.
Gündüz Bey does what he does
for us. Don't you see?
I'll not allow this tribe left from my
father to suffer any more!
From now, if anyone goes against
my word...
I'll consider it against
the bey's words.
Gündüz Bey.
See where you are going before
taking a step.
Don't regret it later.
I know where I step on well, mother.
Bilecik Castle
My valiants.
My alps.
I'm a witness.
You walked on Allah's way.
For the prophet's cause...
you turned your swords...
into Zülfikar and used them on
the heathens!
To tremble the whole world with
the sound of 'Allahu Akbar'...
you took many difficult paths
with me.
Now...
now Yezid will stay a Yezid.
And if our destiny...
is to fall martyr, like the favorite of
our good prophet...
our minister Hüseyin...
it's a grace!
We'll be glad!
-Praise Allah, my bey.
-Praise Allah.
Praise Allah.
My commanders in Bilecik.
Nikola must've bought them.
But there are loyal ones among them.
Who can't be bought with money.
But it's impossible to reach them now.
It's the humans...
they see every opportunity
as if it's from them.
Insolent...
needs to know his place first.
Not you.
The humans.
Allah shows many ways.
When the human can't see them,
he can't reach them.
And if you are so sure of their
loyalty...
I will bring them to you.
They won't say no after
seeing me.
If they are as loyal
as you said...
they won't care who's
calling them.
Lord.
They'll come for you.
I'm grateful.
For everything.
If you can bring my commanders here...
you will learn the news from Osman.
Julia.
Because of her betrayal, Osman is being
kept by Nicola and the vizier.
They will kill him.
They will not let him live.
He will die in vain.
If Osman Bey dies, he will be a martyr.
For the martyrs, it is said that;
"As for those who are killed in the
way of Allah..."
Allah will not let their deeds
be in vain."
Martyr's blood is not shed in vain,
Tekfur.
But I know that...
If I become a martyr...
our case will not bow down.
Even if we die...
the love and faith of Allah...
will always bloom in the hearts of
our children.
Our brave sons will carry on the Islam
that we handed over.
I hope so.
My alps.
The brave alps of Kayi tribe!
I give you all of my blessings.
May Allah give you his blessings too.
I forgive you for all of your faults.
-Forgive me for all of my faults too.
-We forgive you.
We forgive you, my Bey.
We forgive you.
What did you do as a fault?
We give all of our blessings, my Bey.
All of our blessings.
If Osman Bey dies, you will not have
a leader.
How can you be so calm in this
situation?
Do you know Hadhrat Hamza?
Hadhrat Ali?
Hadhrat Osman?
Do you know Zeyd Bin Harise?
Abdullah bin Revaha?
Do you know Cafer bin Ebu Talib?
Do you know Hadhrat Hüseyin?
I don't know. I heard them for
the first time.
How can you know?
Of course, you don't know.
They are such people that...
I would give my life for them.
They were from the stars of the sky,
the sky of Hadhrat Muhammed.
They were the closest ones to him.
Especially, Hüseyin.
He was so precious.
All of them were martyred
for Allah.
We are still feeling the pain.
Such a pain, it is such a pain.
But their deaths are for Allah.
That's why we don't woe.
After them, many people died
in the way of Allah.
If Osman Bey will be a martyr for
this purpose...
let him be.
If we will be in grief, let us be.
We will not woe.
It is enough for us as long as the
belief in Allah lasts forever.
You...
Turks...
you amaze me more and more every day.
I never thought you would think like this.
Allah!
The time of every death is certain.
But it's not the right
time for you, Osman Bey.
Martyrdom is forbidden to you for now.
You will not experience this now.
It is forbidden, Osman Bey.
You...
will...
establish a state first.
Firstly...
you will establish a state.
The secret is solved.
Are you ready to die?
I will watch with great pleasure...
as you swing on the rope.
If we die...
we will be martyrs.
We are not afraid of the rope.
But if we live...
dig yourself a grave...
and go inside.
Soldiers!
The Castle of Harmankaya
Mari.
Soldiers, get this man out of here!
I'm talking to you. You will not let this
man enter my castle again.
Don't you dare! Don't you dare to
get closer to me, Nicola.
If you try to harm me in this castle, you
will pay a heavy price.
Don't be so sure, Mari.
Because this castle is not yours anymore.
Your lovely brother Koses...
tried to kill the vizier with Osman.
So, Koses is a traitor now.
What do we do in this situation
according to the rules?
We give punishment.
Harmankaya...
is mine now.
What did you do to my brother,
Nicola?
He will talk to the
Emperor, not to me, Mari.
Will you give me this castle without
causing any problem or...
should I come with the soldiers
of the Emperor and...
destroy this place?
What should I do?
Never.
I won't even give you garbage.
Soldiers.
Eventually, Samuel. Get this man
out of here.
Agios Nikola, me and my soldiers
are waiting for your orders.
Soldiers, lower the flags!
No. No! Don't you dare to touch them!
Don't touch!
Don't touch me!
Leave me!
How could you do this, traitor?!
Samuel.
Take your most loyal soldiers.
And kill everyone who you
suspect of their loyalty.
I don't want any mistakes.
And also, that new groom.
What was his name?
Turgut.
If he comes to the castle, kill him.
Don't even hesitate. Don't let him
leave this castle alive.
You will never be able to do this,
Nikola.
You will regret what you did!
Shut up, don't talk!
Leave her alone! Don't touch her!
Cornelia!
Argus.
Take Mari to my castle.
I don't like my work being left
unfinished.
We have an issue to finish.
But this time it will not be that easy,
Mari.
You should've died that day.
Now my anger is stronger, Mari.
See you at İnegöl.
The Castle of Bilecik
Osman will be hanged first.
And then, his soldiers.
You came at the most opportune
time, Nikola.
I came here as soon as possible
after I seize the Castle of Harmankaya.
I can't miss such a moment.
You don't know how long I've been
waiting for today, Vizier Alemşah.
Today is my celebration day.
We will see many celebration
days together, Nikola.
Die, die!
Eventually.
Eventually!
Die!
O Allah, the victor!
Will we wait like this?
After all this, are we going to leave
Osman to the mercy of the Sultan?
Of course, we will not, Bala.
We can't trust Sultan Mesud anymore.
It is the vizier of the Sultan who
brought these matters to us.
There are no alps, what will we do?
I will take the alps that are loyal to
Osman.
We will save Osman in the way of Konya.
You're outnumbered. How will you win?
This time, I will come too.
I will not leave Osman alone.
What are you talking about?
You're entrusted to me by Osman.
I don't want to put both you and your
child in danger.
And our people need a head.
Stay there and take care of them.
Osman attempted evil to break
the friendship...
we established with the Emperor.
He opposed the order of the Seljuk Empire.
Cut it short. Come on, come on!
I, Vizier Alemşah...
I am here to put the ones who
oppose the order in their place.
Whoever tries...
to overshadow the order
established by the Seljuk Empire...
his fate...
will be hanged like Osman.
Now...
you will pay for this rebellion, Osman.
Come on. Come on.
If you had obeyed, that rope
would not be around your neck now.
You tried to kill the vizier of the
Seljuk Empire.
Now, you will pay for this.
Both I and...
my valiants...
prefer to die in the way of Allah...
rather than...
living a dishonorable life.
Living a dishonorable life...
suits the ones like you, Vizier Alemşah.
It is obvious that you are from
Yezidis (a community).
We believe that...
there is no victor other than Allah!
And we do not bow before anyone but Allah.
O Allah, the victor!
Reciting the kalima shahadah (confessing
his belief in Allah)
Come on, now! Come on!
Eventually!
Who did this?!
Do you have a death wish?!
Sultan Mesud did this, Vizier Alemşah.
His order is certain.
My Bey, we are alright.
We are alright.
How can it be possible?
Osman is a rebel who tried to kill me.
His death is obligatory.
Sultan Mesud's order is certain.
He wants him taken to Konya.
If his death was obligatory...
we wouldn't save him.
Is a rebel's life more precious than the
life of the vizier of the Seljuk Empire?
Is that why you prevented his death?
The order is from the Sultan.
Not fulfilling the order and killing
Osman here...
which is a rebellious act...
means opposing Sultan Mesud.
In that case, I would take you...
not Osman, Vizier Alemşah.
You saved both my and my alps' life.
Thank you.
Our problem is not your
or your alps' life.
Sultan Mesud wants to secure
justice in Konya.
Where was justice...
when Vizier Alemşah was doing
things that were full of lies against...
Sultan Mesud all this time?
Why Konya is too slow to act?
The state arrives at its destination...
neither early nor late.
If we are here now, it is because the
state wanted us to be here now.
Come on, we are going.
You made a big mistake, Vizier
Alemşah.
It is such a big mistake. When you had
the chance, you should've killed Osman.
I told you to hurry!
Where did this sergeant hear that
we were going to hang Osman?
Vizier Alemşah is working
against the Sultan.
He will hang Osman Bey without a
reason in the square of Bilecik.
I know your problem so well,
Vizier Alemşah.
But you will not be able to
achieve your goal.
No one will know that I told you this.
Even Osman Bey will think that he is saved
thanks to the order of Sultan Mesud.
Don't worry.
For the survival of the state, our
friends will not know our friendship...
and our enemies will not know our
enmity.
Get ready. We are going to Bilecik.
That means the Sultan is watching
Bilecik too.
I am the one who send him the news
from both here and Konya.
There is a hidden catch here.
And I will find that.
But first, I'll take care of Osman.
What Osman, Vizier Alemşah?!
You'll take care of Osman?!
He went away in front of our eyes!
Don't be so sure, Agios Nikola.
Osman will never be able to reach Konya.
Miss, how will we escape?
Landlord Koses and Turgut
Bey are not around.
How will we escape?
Don't be afraid, Cornelia. Don't be
afraid.
They will not be able to do anything
to us if we are not afraid.
Turgut!
Come on!
No!
I will cut those hands that
touched my woman.
Come.
My Bey, they are coming!
Alps, we are withdrawing!
Cornelia, come here.
Hurry up.
Find them all!
Consider yourself dead if you come
to İnegöl without finding them!
Come on, alps!
We are going to take Osman Bey.
It is war day, it is hard to turn back.
Those who can take the risk should come.
The command is yours, Malhun Hatun.
Come here.
My Bey.
Lord's soldiers lost track of us.
Good.
That Koses. What will I do with
your brother now, Mari?
I told you that he is unreliable.
It was not my brother this time, Turgut.
His life is in danger too.
My brothers and Osman Bey were caught.
They will take my
brother to Constantinople.
What are you talking about, Mari?
Osman Bey too?
Do you know where they keep them?
I don't know.
The vizier and Nikola.
They seized the castle. What will
we do now?
Okay. Keep calm.
By the way, how did you learn that
I was kidnapped?
You didn't have to come, my Bey.
We would collect the taxes.
Thank you.
But it's Osman Bey's order.
How can I reject?
I can't. Remember what Osman Bey
did for us.
Alright.
My Bey. Turgut Bey.
What happened?
Nikola came to the castle and seized it.
Mari Hatun is kidnapped.
What are you talking about?
They took her to İnegöl.
Nikola.
If you touch even a single
strand of her hair...
I will tear you into pieces.
Come on, alps!
Don't worry, Mari.
We will save your brother, Koses.
And of course, Osman Bey too.
I'm so glad that I have you.
Firstly, Koses.
It is obvious that Osman Bey
is in danger with his alps.
Gündüz Bey and the vizier are
like a hand in the glove.
You are saying that we need Kossess
and his soldiers, my Bey.
Get ready, Kutan.
We will save Osman Bey with Koses.
As you ordered, my Bey.
I will come too.
No, Mari.
What are you saying?
Where will I go then, Turgut?
To the place where I was kidnapped
or to the castle that Nİkola seized?
Damn!
How will I tell this to Nikola?
There you go, brother! Run! Run! Run!
Come on, brother!
Osman Bey.
We have already known that you
will do such a thing.
Alright, only one was able to go.
Has anyone heard that we do not
obey?
Osman Bey.
Osman Bey, we know you as a son
of a Bey...
and respect you.
And you should know that we are
the state and we saved...
you from the rope in the name of Konya.
We know you from your
ancestor, Ertuğrul Ghazi.
We've been on the road for a long time.
I didn't talk.
Talking with a rebel is not
good behavior.
But my ancestor Turan Bey
was used to talk about...
your ancestor, Ertuğrul Ghazi.
They fought together in many wars.
Those who came to me always mentioned...
the state first and then the respect.
Sergeant İlgezdi, I don't trust anyone.
Not every treacherous-looking person
will work against you, Osman Bey.
It is like a good in the bad.
Let's go to the presence of
the Sultan first.
With his justice, you will be absolved
from guilt.
Thank you.
We do not forget the good or the bad.
Soldiers, we are going.
You stay there.
I'm his killer slave.
Come.
Grapes.
Vizier Alemşah.
Loser dies.
But...
...I don't lose.
No doubt.
You are the leader of the armies that
make the bravest shake...
...and break steel wrists, Geyhatu.
I don't like talking too much.
Did you kill Osman?
No.
I reserved him for you.
He is under arrest now.
He is going to Konya.
But Osman can't reach Konya.
Whatever we must--
He won't!
But why? Does he know that...
...we will dethrone the Sultan?
No, Osman will find a way to cause
trouble.
The sergeant who is bringing Osman
is a brave man.
Be careful.
Standing against a Mogul is difficult.
How challenging can be a Seljuk soldier?
They are using the road around
the Akman Mountain.
Their horses must be tired now.
They must spend the night at the cave.
They will take my Osman Bey on his
way to Konya.
But they are few people, my Sheik.
I am afraid that something will happen.
Malhun Hatun will catch up with Osman
Bey, if Allah lets.
Don't worry, Bala Hatun.
Osman Bey survived many hardships.
He will get through this too, I hope.
I hope.
Wheat will certainly turn into ears.
This is how it is...
...wheat will go through
many difficult things...
...until it mixes with the ground
and sprouts.
It will be watered and grown
by the mercy of my Rabb.
It will grow out to be a spike.
Wind will blow, the sun will warm it up...
...the day will come and that spike will
grow.
And it will stand still.
Are you saying Osman Bey is a seed
planted for these lands?
Is that so?
Is it easy to grow on the ground
and reach for the sky?
It will be paninful.
It will be big.
We will say the earth is about to crack,
the seed is about to grow...
...but Allah will tell us to wait.
Wait, so your root gets stronger.
Wait, so that your enemies can't hurt
you...
...until you reach the sky.
When poison ivy thinks it killed
you..
...you will return stronger.
Osman Bey.
His challenge is hard, his enemy is
evil.
But...
...the love in his heart...
...will defeat all his enemies.
This blessed cause will take over
these lands.
Osman's generation will freely spread
the justice of Allah...
...and the cause of the Prophet
to the whole world.
I hope.
Be of good cheer.
This cause will not be left without
a leader.
-I hope.
Selamun Aleykum.
Ve Aleykumselam.
Aleykumselam.
Mari?
What happened?
I don't have good news.
Nowhere is safe. Thus, Turgut sent me
to you.
You know about the tribe.
Nikola took over Harmankaya too.
From now on, you are under our protection
my girl.
Is there any news from Osman Bey?
Aygül, you hold there.
We will attack with my signal.
Alaca and you will come with me.
We will do whatever it takes to save
Osman Bey.
As you order, Malhun Hatun.
There will be a Kayı Tribe without us...
...but not without Osman Bey!
Come on! Let's go!
Come on.
They will go through this route.
We will catch them here.
But we are few.
Too few.
We will be careful.
Yes?
My Bey, Vizier is taking Osman Bey
to Konya.
I knew this would happen!
Oh, Vizier! He will be strictly cautious
this time.
Listen to me, alps!
We need Kosses and his men for
Osman Bey.
We will first save Kosses and then
Yes, my Bey!
What if we asked for the tribe's help,
my Bey?
Gündüz Bey can't see the truth that
we see.
Even if it's death in the end,
we'll handle this ourselves.
Come on, valiants!
Let's go!
Alps!
For Osman Bey!
Let Osman Bey go!
We won't leave without him!
Who are you?
I am Malhun Hatun. Daughter of Umur Bey.
Hatun of Osman Bey.
Let my Bey go!
I am glad we met.
But we can't release Osman Bey.
The Sultan gave an order.
We have to go to Konya.
Come on, get out.
We won't return until we take Osman
Bey.
Alps!
Malhun Hatun, you are a few people.
Don't die for nothing.
We have a duty. Open the road.
You can keep your duty. I am taking
Osman Bey!
The easy way or the hard way.
-Alps!
-Malhun.
Stop for a second.
Stop for a second!
Fighting Turk to Turk doesn't suit us.
Especially spilling the blood of a Turk
because of me.
Do I have permission?
I want to talk to my Hatun.
Ah, Malhun, ah!
-My Bey.
-My Malhun.
Don't go, Osman.
We don't know what the Sultan will do.
I can't let you go like this.
Malhun.
We are outnumbered.
I have to go.
Otherwise, we will lose many valiants.
I can never let that happen.
My Bey.
I am afraid that Sultan may be under
the Vizier's influence.
What if he believed his lies?
Don't wor--
Don't worry.
With the help of my Mighty Rabb, I will
go to Konya and return.
After I return, they will pay for what
they have done to us!
Don't worry.
I hope, my Osman.
I hope.
But my only wish is...
...for you to take care of Bala
and Orhan.
Take care of each other.
Take care of the tribe.
I will, my Osman.
But...
...Gündüz Bey is gathering...
...the Assembly of Beys. What will we do
about that, my Bey?
That Gündüz Bey...
...will pay for sitting on Ertugrul Gazi's
seat.
Do whatever it takes to prevent him from
gathering the Assembly of Beys.
The only obstacle on the Turk's way...
...is Alemşah.
And he is working with him.
He is following his ways.
Güzdüz Bey is blind to the truth.
He can't sit on that throne.
What did they do to you?
It doesn't hurt.
Bless your right.
We may not return.
Don't say that!
Don't say that, Cerkutay.
Osman Bey and you will return safe and
sound.
I will wait for you.
Will you?
I will.
Osman Bey!
Come on!
We need to move on.
Be careful, my Osman.
Don't worry at all.
Come on.
Come on Alps!
We need to catch
the Assembly of Beys!
Come on!
Something happened.
I can tell.
What is it?
Turgut...
So?
Ambushed us on our way to İnegöl.
They took Mari, Sir.
We tried to resist but we couldn't.
Most of the soldiers died.
But you are alive.
Right, Argus?
Huh? Idiot Argus!
Good for nothing Argus!
Since he got Mari...
...his move is clear.
Kosses.
And where is Kosses?
On the Constantinople way.
On the horses!
You didn't leave me for more money.
I am grateful to you.
We are sorry we couldn't prevent this
disgrace, Lord Rogatus.
No, no.
It is no time to talk about the past.
Nikola...
...Vizier...
...whoever betrayed me...
...we will make them all pay.
We are here for this, Sir. We'll do
whatever you need.
Now, return to the castle.
Continue to act as if you are not aware
of anything.
I am going to Constantinople.
I will return with good news.
Thank you.
Come on, enjoy!
Alps!
Enjoy!
You are very willing to take us.
Do you trust the state of Konya?
There is not much to worry, Osman Bey.
A fading star.
Why are we going then?
I trust Sultan Mesud. You get clear
with his justice so that...
...a new star can shine.
But the Vizier...
...is confusing the Sultan.
He is the same as a snake.
Venomous.
The fate of the snake we catch
is obvious.
He will pay for what he's done too.
The power to make them pay is within
the Kayı!
Why?
Why do you trust us?
Are you the only Kayı people, huh?
Kayı is everywhere.
Serving the same purpose.
Liberty of the Turks!
Sultan Mesud's order is above anything.
Otherwise, I would be throwing
swords with you now.
When I get clear...
...we will.
We will.
Thank you.
I promised Vizier Alemşah.
The Assembly will take place tomorrow!
What are you doing, Hatuns?
What are you doing, Gündüz Bey?
We brought news from the Bey of Kayı.
Who is it?
Osman is prisoned, Bala Hatun.
Güzdüz Bey...
...you forgot but the actual owner
of the throne is Osman Bey.
We met with my Bey on his way to Konya.
Osman Bey says that no matter...
...what the price is, I will return to my
tribe!
He said he will sit on the throne
he took from Ertuğrul Gazi again.
And he said that he will behead anyone if
he...
...is sitting there when he returns.
My valiant...
...Osman Bey!
He doesn't leave his tribe!
Would Kayı Tribe ever suffer when it
has such a Bey?
If Osman Bey said so, he will return.
Osman Bey will come back!
We need Osman Bey for the sake of
the tribe!
It is the order of the Vizier!
The Assembly will take place!
Osman Bey's order, the Assembly
will not take place!
My Bey is not here, but we are.
We won't let it happen!
It is the order of the state!
Everyone will obey!
You too!
Osman included!
If anyone can, let them come...
...and stop us.
Brothers...
...we may not but...
...my Bey has a dream...
...but they do anything to stop him.
How could this happen?
We just escaped the ropes.
About Konya, we don't know what
will happen.
May Allah help us.
Amen.
If it is up to Allah, then it is done,
brothers.
My Bey will get out of this trouble.
Of course.
But how, brother?
My Bey is such a bey that...
... he helped many, he saved many.
Of course, he bothers the tyrants.
He does.
That's why they play many games
to him, they slander him.
Therefore...
...what we must do is stay strong...
...without a doubt.
This will all end, if Allah lets.
My homeland is also crushed under
the Mongol persecution.
Welcome, brother.
We are glad but why did you come?
Hope is here, brother.
Hope is within Osman Bey.
He leads the fight.
Wherever Jihad is, the Muslim
considers it homeland.
Mashallah to my brother!
When we get through these days and I
get my swords back...
...we will fight many battles, I hope.
Thank you.
Thanks to my Allah for getting our paths
together.
Thank you, brother.
Thank you.
Seljuks and Osman are in the cave.
We can go and rip off their heads.
How many soldiers are around the cave?
Many.
A cave is a good place to defend.
They may resist. We will wait for them
to leave the cave in the morning.
We will hit them on the road.
Then, you
can rip off as many heads as you want.
Is Osman's gift well?
For now.
Good.
Osman is a brave man.
But he is an obstacle for my goals.
He will be gone.
Osman.
I need Alemşah.
And he needs your death.
Argun Han will die.
Sultan Mesud will die.
You will die.
The Khan of all these lands...
...will be me!
You!
Brother!
My Bey!
Brother.
Are you all right, my Bey?
The Sergeant is waiting outside, my Bey.
Brother.
My brother won't sit on the throne.
Let alone the state we will establish...
...he wants to destroy the existing one.
My Bey.
There is Malhun Hatun...
...Bala Hatun.
Selcen Mother, Aygül.
There is Göktuğ brother, my Bey.
He will of course go to the tribe.
They will stop them, my Bey.
Yes, Cerkutay. The hatuns will stop him.
They will.
The throne...
...will wait for its real owner.
There is also Turgut Bey!
He will come for us as soon as he hears
about us, my Bey.
Yes, he is our brother.
Kosses!
Where are you going without avenging
your sister?
Let no one touch his sword so that...
...women do not become widows
and children orphans.
Come on!
Just in time!
Look who is here!
As Turgut Bey said, don't touch your
swords.
Otherwise Mari will both become
a widow and...
...what do you call a person whose
brother is dead?
You!
I don't know. It doesn't matter.
Tragedy.
I love it.
Geyhatu!
Osman...
...we met again!
I stopped you for a gift.
Bring him!
Göktuğ!
Brother!
My Bey!
Kongar or Göktuğ!
He was a Mogul!
He grew up like a Mongolian!
You turned him into a Turk!
This makes you a good leader and a
dangerous enemy.
You will die, Osman!
But first...
...this traitor.
Every heart that beats for rebellion
is doomed to be pierced.
Don't you dare!
If you pierce his heart...
...the fire for revenge in me and in every
Turk...
...will burn you alive!
My Bey!
Geyhatu thinks...
...he can break us.
But we come alive the more we die!
Death is inevitable.
But...
...dying with my brothers...
...and my Bey on the right path...
... is my consolation.
A death like this can only strengthen us.
-No!
-Göktuğ!
No!
Göktuğ!
Brother!
Geyhatu!
Let me go!
I bear witness that there is
no god but Allah...
No! Göktuğ!
Göktuğ!
...and I bear witness that Muhammad--
You dog!
... is the servant and Messenger
of Allah.
Brother!
Göktuğ!
Göktuğ! My brother!
Let me go!
Göktuğ!
If I do not shed...
... the blood of 1000 oppressors
for the blood of a single Turk...
...then my name is not Osman!
You are the leader of the oppressor,
Geyhatu!
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com